## Ing. Michal Sokirka

**IT Support Analyst** 

#### Contact

- ntienica, Slovakia
- 🔀 sokirka.michal@gmail.com
- +421 917 88 53 84

#### Education

2002 - 2011

Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Information Technology in Bratislava

1998 - 2002 Secondary School of Electro technology in Prešov

### Skills

MS Windows Server – administration
MS SQL Server – basic administration
SQL scripting – basics
IIS – advanced
PC Hardware – advanced
PowerShell scripting – skillful
Windows Batch scripting – skillful
Octopus Deploy tool – skillful
Computer networking – basics
Python – basics
Typescript, React, NestJS – basics
Linux – basics

### Languages

Slovak – native English – fluent

#### **Profile**

With over ten years of experience in application support, I bring a strong track record of delivering reliable technical solutions and ensuring high levels of customer satisfaction—always my top priority. I'm now seeking a new opportunity where I can take on fresh challenges, continue growing professionally, and contribute to a team that values continuous improvement.

### Work experience

## IT Support Analyst at AFS Visicom Slovakia a.s. 2019 – 2024

Installing and supporting Supply Chain Management systems (ERP, WMS, OMS, Gateway) and IIS based web applications. Installing SQL server. Migrating and upgrading applications. Troubleshooting complex technical issues in cooperation with the development department. Moving towards DevOps model. Migrating manual installation process to new continuous deployment process using Octopus Deploy tool. Writing/maintaining installation scripts mostly in PowerShell.

Creating and maintaining install documentation.

## L2 Technical Support Specialist at Gamanet a.s. 2013 – 2019

Supporting installation partners over the phone and emails. Providing remote assistance and troubleshooting application issues. Resolving problems related to installing the application and connecting it to all kinds of building security hardware such as Access control systems, Alarm systems, Fire protection systems and CCTV systems. Reading relevant log files. Helping L1 Support team members. Fulfilling tasks related to the position of Deputy Head of Support.

## Technician Support Centre agent at AT&T 2012 – 2013

Supporting end users. Providing L2 & L3 support for internal smartphone, iPad and Windows users via phone. Accessing user's Windows device remotely in order to solve difficult issues with software or printers. Daily communication with customers over the phone and/or e-mail. Setting up the devices according to the user's needs. Helping users to resolve issues with e-mail/Microsoft Outlook on a mobile device as well as on PC/Laptop.

# Windows 1st line support agent at Ajilon [UK] Ltd. 2009 – 2011

Remotely managing HP servers based on Windows platform. Connecting to devices (servers, printers) for troubleshooting purposes. Documenting the troubleshooting steps using workflow management tools. Communication with customers. Performing health-checks on servers. Setting permissions for shared folders according to customer's request. Checking databases and resolving basic DB issues. Escalating unresolved issues to higher level or to an on-site technician if needed.